Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/janmejay-das-2359665b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

PL/SQL

Data Structures

Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Oriya (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

JavaScript and AJAX

Java: Testing with JUnit

Java: Data Structures

Janmejay Das

Senior Engineer at Shopee

Singapore

Summary

Experienced Software Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and banking industry.

Highly skilled in Java/J2EE,PL/SQL,Bigdata, JBoss/WebLogic Application Server, Spring Framework, Spring boot with Microservices and strong hand in Data Structures and algorithms.

Strong engineering professional with a Master of Computer Applications (MCA) focused in Computer Programming, Specific Applications from Manipal Institute of Technology.

Experience

Shopee

Senior Engineer

December 2020 - Present (4 months)

Singapore

Crédit Agricole CIB

Java Developer

March 2019 - December 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Singapore

Oracle

Application Engineer 2

March 2017 - March 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Hyderabad Area, India

Intellect Design Arena Ltd

Consultant

July 2014 - February 2017 (2 years 8 months)

Hyderabad

Polaris Financial Technology Ltd.

Page 1 of 2

Intern

January 2014 - June 2014 (6 months)

Hyderabad

Education

Manipal Institute of Technology

Master of Computer Applications (MCA), Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2011 - 2014)

North Orissa University

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Mathematics · (2008 - 2011)